supabase functions deploy ai-brains-agency
Deployed Functions on project dbclmdeowohzmwtkktsa: ai-brains-agency
You can inspect your deployment in the Dashboard: https://supabase.com/dashboard/project/dbclmdeowohzmwtkktsa/functions
supabase functions deploy ai-brains-client
Deployed Functions on project dbclmdeowohzmwtkktsa: ai-brains-client
You can inspect your deployment in the Dashboard: https://supabase.com/dashboard/project/dbclmdeowohzmwtkktsa/functions
supabase functions deploy ai-documents-ingest
Deployed Functions on project dbclmdeowohzmwtkktsa: ai-documents-ingest
You can inspect your deployment in the Dashboard: https://supabase.com/dashboard/project/dbclmdeowohzmwtkktsa/functions
supabase functions deploy ai-ask
Deployed Functions on project dbclmdeowohzmwtkktsa: ai-ask
You can inspect your deployment in the Dashboard: https://supabase.com/dashboard/project/dbclmdeowohzmwtkktsa/functions
